Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Roy Glah papers, 1947-2003 and undated RL.00704
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Roy Glah papers
1947-2003 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
RL.00704
1172
33.0 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. Roy Glah was an executive and assistant to the CEO at the JWT New York Office. Includes correspondence and memoranda, research reports, presentations, speeches and other printed materials. Non-print materials include slides, audio and video cassettes, and computer discs. Materials primarily relate to top-level management of JWT, coordination between international offices, corporate vision and long-term strategy, interaction with parent company WPP. A significant portion of materials pertain to logistics and planning for executive-level meetings and conferences and client presentations. Companies represented include Bell Atlantic, Ford, Kellogg, Kodak, Nestle, Philip Morris, Rolex, Unilever and Warner-Lambert. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
However, original audiovisual and computer materials are closed to research until use copies can be produced.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Roy Glah papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as gifts in 1999, 2000, 2004 and 2005.
Biographical Note
Biographical Chronology
1935 Dec. Born, Philadelphia, Penn.
1957 Began work with JWT New York Office, Creative Department BFA, Cornell University
Circa 1958-1960 Military service
1960 Media Department, JWT New York
1963 Account Representative, JWT New York
1964 JWT Amsterdam
Circa 1967 General Manager, JWT Amsterdam
1968 Account Supervisor, JWT New York
1972 Senior Vice President and Deputy Manager, JWT Tokyo
1974 Manager, JWT San Francisco
1977 Assistant to the Chairman, JWT New York
1982 Senior Vice President, Operations, JWT New York
1984 Deputy General Manager, JWT New York
1987 Elected Director, JWT
1988 elected to U.S. Board of Directors Elected Executive Vice President, Finance and Administration, JWT/USA
1990 Management Director, JWT
Collection Overview
Includes correspondence and memoranda, research reports, presentations, speeches and other printed materials. Non-print materials include slides, audio and video cassettes, and computer discs. Materials primarily relate to top-level management of JWT, coordination between international offices, corporate vision and long-term strategy, interaction with parent company WPP. A significant portion of materials pertain to logistics and planning for executive-level meetings and conferences and client presentations. Companies represented include Bell Atlantic, Ford, Kellogg, Kodak, Nestle, Philip Morris, Rolex, Unilever and Warner-Lambert. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Account Files; Biographical Information; Burt Manning papers; International Offices records; Thompson Way/Thompson Total Branding records; Writings and Speeches; WPP Group records
Speeches, addresses, etc., American; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising executives; Advertising agencies -- Management; Advertising -- United States; Manning, Burt, 1931-; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; J. Walter Thompson Company; Glah, Roy, 1935-; Bell Atlantic Corporation; Ford Motor Company; Kellogg Company; Eastman Kodak Company; Nestlé; Philip Morris Incorporated; Montres Rolex S.A.; Unilever (Firm); Warner-Lambert Company
- General Files, 1974-2001 and undated; 1
  - AAAA agency cost surveys, 1985-1994; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - "Abruption" project--Binder, 1993; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - "Abruption" project--Case histories, 1993; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - "Abruption" project--Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 2)
  - "Abruption" project--Nina DiSesa binder, 1994 (Box 2)
  - "Abruption" project--Videotape production, 1993-1994; 5 folders (Box 2)
  - Account management performance evaluation summary, undated (Box 3)
  - Agency "Dissatisfaction" survey, 1994; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Agency image/reputation, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - All Offices Management Review, 1991; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Bell Atlantic--Corporate identity program, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Bell Atlantic--Managing the Bell Atlantic Brand, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Bell Atlantic--Presentation, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Bell Atlantic--Project Utopia, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Benefits program, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Board of Directors candidates, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Brouillard Communications--Financial Review, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Brouillard Communications--Financial Review, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Burt Manning--Press, photographs, etc., 1987-1993 (Box 4)
  - Burt Manning--Staff photographs, undated (Box 4)
  - Burt Manning--Video tribute (Thompson Total Manning), 1996 (Box 4)
  - CEO review, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Champions Institute, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Chicago Office--Case studies, circa 1993 (Box 66)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes: 7-Eleven Slurpee; Oscar Mayer Lunchables; Kraft Miracle Whip
  - Chicago Office--Computer proposal, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Chicago Office--Operating Committee, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Chicago Office--What's It Like in Chicago?, circa 1994 (Box 4)
  - Client-Agency Evaluations, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Client Assessment Grid, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Client Conflict Reference Manual, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Coherent philosophy for JWT, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Communications Futures Group, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Competing agencies' mission statements, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Competitive Comparative Advertising video project, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Connect 2000 Plan, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Corporate Communications Operating Plan, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Detroit Office telephone directory, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Diamond Trading Company Review, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Executive Brief for 2002 Strategic I.T. Plan, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Finance--1997 Q3RF vs. 1996 Actual (Box 5)
  - Finance--1998 Q2 vs. Budget (Box 5)
  - Finance--2002 Budget, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Finance--Departmental salary analysis, 1996 (Box 65)
  - Finance--Multinational Client Profitability, 1996-1998; 4 folders (Box 5)
  - Finance--Salary to Revenue, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Financial data, 1996-1998 (Box 6)
  - Ford--Global Business Plan, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Ford--Things We've Learned, undated (Box 6)
  - Ford--Thompson Total Branding, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Former Directors, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Global Business--Key Points, circa 1998 (Box 6)
  - Global Business--Partnerships Operating Principles, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Global Business--Reports, 1998-2001; 4 folders (Box 6)
  - Global Business--Status Report, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Global Media Group, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Global Media Research Group, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Global Reviews, 2001 (Box 6)
  - How JWT Sees Itself, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Human Resources Group, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Human Resources Group, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Human Resources organization, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Internal communications survey, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Internet advertising--Legal issues, 1996 (Box 7)
  - J. Walter Technology, undated (Box 7)
  - J. Walter Technology, 1994 (Box 65)
  - JWT Asia Pacific, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - JWT Asia Pacific--Budget, 1999 (Box 7)
  - JWT Asia Pacific--Developing the "Big Match" Temperament, 1994 (Box 7)
  - JWT Asia Pacific--Gains and losses, 2001 (Box 7)
  - JWT brand, 1993 (Box 7)
  - JWT Canada overview, 1991 (Box 7)
  - JWT Direct, 1997 (Box 7)
  - JWT Entertainment Services, 1994 (Box 7)
  - JWT Entertainment Services--Business plan, 1997 (Box 7)
  - JWT Europe--New business, 1991 (Box 7)
  - JWT Europe--Reports, 1991 (Box 8)
  - JWT Europe--Viewpoint East, 1991 (Box 8)
  - JWT Europe--Where Today's Action Is!, circa 1991 (Box 8)
  - JWT Europe, Middle East and Asia, 2001 (Box 8)
  - JWT Headquarter Services, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - JWT Hong Kong--A New Way of Working, circa 1994 (Box 8)
  - JWT Innovation Centre, undated (Box 8)
  - JWT Latin America, 1994 (Box 8)
  - JWT Latin America--2000 Budget Review, 1999 (Box 8)
  - JWT Latin America and Caribbean, 2001 (Box 8)
  - JWT Latin American Managers Meeting, 1991 (Box 8)
  - JWT London Budget Review, 1997 (Box 8)
  - JWT management structure, 1997 (Box 8)
  - JWT Office Public Relations Plans, 1989 (Box 8)
  - JWT Skillset/Turnover Analysis, 1998 (Box 8)
  - JWT South East Asia Review, circa 1992 (Box 9)
  - JWT Strategic Plan, circa 1994 (Box 9)
  - JWT USA--1990 +3-Year Goals (Box 9)
  - JWT USA--Partner and Senior Partner recommendations, 1995 (Box 9)
  - JWT USA--The Vital Signs, 1991 (Box 9)
  - JWT/West--Innovations, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Kellogg account review, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Kodak account loss, 1997 (Box 9)
  - Kraft--Coffee overview, 1995; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Kraft--Worldwide Board of Directors, 1997 (Box 9)
  - Leadership Aptitude and Practices Survey (LAPS), 1995 (Box 9)
  - Long-range plan, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Long-range plan, 1990-1996; 4 folders (Box 10)
  - Los Angeles Office, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Making Sense of Green Marketing, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Management assignments, retirements, etc., 1994 (Box 10)
  - Management organization, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Management succession plans, 1994-1996; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Management titles project, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Management Vision and Mission, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Management vision statement, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Mapping the Information Highway, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Media Challenge of the 1990s, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Mindshare, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Multinational status report, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Nestle-JWT Relationship update, 2001 (Box 11)
  - New Business Support Briefing and Work Plan, circa 1997 (Box 11)
  - North America Q3RF Review, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Northern Telecom advertising overview, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Odyssey of the Commodore, undated (Box 11)
  - Overview and Application of a JWT Brand Power Index, circa 1997 (Box 11)
  - Paperweight--Facsimile of JWT Group advertisement for common stock share offer, 1983 (Box AV5)
  - Philip Morris global business plan, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Press and publicity, 1996-1998; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Press clips, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Procedural Overview for Using the MNL Status Reports Database in Lotus Notes, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Prodigy positioning, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Professional skills criteria, circa 1994 (Box 12)
  - Quotes--James Webb Young, undated (Box 12)
  - Quotes--Stanley Resor, undated (Box 12)
  - Restructured Board of Directors, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Rolex--Atlantic Challenge Cup, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Rolex--Co-Op Advertising material, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
  - Rolex--Co-Op Advertising portfolio, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Rolex--Co-Op Advertising portfolio, 1997 (Box 65)
  - Rolex--International Advertising Proposals, 1992-1994; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Rolex--International Advertising Proposals, 1994-1995; 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Rolex--Print advertisement, circa 1997 (Box 66)
  - Rolex--U.S. creative, circa 1997 (Box 13)
  - Servicing Sprint: A Client Perspective, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Simmons Market Research Bureau, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Strategic Development (Ten pillars), 1996 (Box 13)
  - Strategic plans, 1989-1999; 4 folders (Box 13)
  - Strategic plans, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Strategic plans--Binder, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Strategic plans--Making It Happen, 1995 (Box 14)
  - Strategic plans--Memos, 1994-1995 (Box 14)
  - Strategic plans--Review, 1996 (Box 14)
  - Strategic plans--Summary, undated (Box 14)
  - Strategic plans--Work draft, 1996; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Strategic review 2000-2002, 1999 (Box 14)
  - T-Plan--Advertising Planning Methods, 1987 (Box 15)
  - T-Plan--Canada--Target Planning, 1980 (Box 15)
  - T-Plan--Chicago--An Approach to Planning Effective Advertising, 1977 (Box 15)
  - T-Plan--Guide to the T-Plan, 1985 (Box 15)
  - T-Plan--JWT London Planning Guide, 1974 (Box 15)
  - T-Plan--New York--Guide to the T-Plan, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Thompson Total Branding, 1996 (Box 15)
  - Thompson Total Transformation, undated (Box 15)
  - Three-Year Plan, 1992-1994; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Three-Year Plan--Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 15)
  - Three-Year Plan--Response to WPP questions, 1993 (Box 15)
  - Top 100 Project, 1996; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Trademark search: Maximiser, 1996 (Box 16)
  - Unilever--Global Business Plan, 1996 (Box 16)
  - Unilever--Project Planner, 1997 (Box 16)
  - Videotape projects, 1994 (Box 16)
  - Videotapes in Burt Manning's conference room, speech file, 1995-1996 (Box 16)
  - Warner-Lambert--Adams Division Client Executive Group Review, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Warner-Lambert--Consumer Healthcare Global Relationship Assessment Board, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Wolverine presentation with slides, 1991; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - World Partners Council, 1995-1997; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - World Partners Council--Brand/Client Consultancy, 1995 (Box 17)
  - World Partners Council--Questionnaire responses, 1997 (Box 17)
  - World Partners Council--Strategic Plan, 1995 (Box 17)
  - World Partners Council--Technology Consultancy, 1995 (Box 17)
  - Worldwide account gains and losses, 1998 (Box 17)
  - Worldwide creative awards, 1994 (Box 17)
  - Worldwide Operating Group (WWOG) objectives, 1992 and undated (Box 17)
  - WPP, 1988-1995; 5 folders (Box 17)
  - WPP, 1993-1995 (Box 18)
  - WPP--Specialist Communications, 1995 (Box 18)
  - WPP--Worldwide Partnership Program, 1998 (Box 18)
- Meetings, 1993-2002; 2
  - General, 1993-2002; 1
    - The Americas, 1996-1997; 5 folders (Box 18)
    - Board of Directors, 1997; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Brand Executive/Client Executive, 1998; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Brand Summit (Niagara), 1998; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Business Week Interviews, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Commodore Club, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Client Executive, 1998; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Client Executive, 1998 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence, December meetings, 2001 (Box 20)
    - EXCO Group, 1999; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Financial Analysts, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Financial Analysts, 1994-1996; 5 folders (Box 21)
    - Financial Operations, 1998; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Financial/Operations Review, 1995-1996; 6 folders (Box 22)
    - Financial/Operations Review, 1996; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - General Managers, 1994 (Box 23)
    - General Managers--Summary, 1994 (Box 23)
    - Global Business, 1997 (Box 23)
    - Global Business Review, 2001 (Box 23)
    - Global Financial Review, 2001 (Box 23)
    - Global Media Council Workshop, 1997 (Box 23)
    - Institutional Investors, 1994; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - JWT senior management meeting with Robert Byrd (Duke University), 1995 (Box 24)
    - Key meetings material, 1998 (Box 24)
    - Latin American Managers, 1995 (Box 24)
    - Management Meeting Summaries, 1994-1997; 4 folders (Box 24)
    - Management Meeting Summaries, 1998 (Box 25)
    - Marti Flores Prieto & Wachtel, 1999 (Box 25)
    - Meetings ground rules, circa 2002 (Box 25)
    - Multinational accounts, 1995 (Box 25)
    - North American Financial Review, 2001 (Box 25)
    - North American Management, 1995 (Box 25)
    - North American Management--Dorothy Marcus public relations presentation, 1995 (Box 25)
    - North American Managers, 1998; 3 folders (Box 25)
    - North American Managers, 1998 (Box 26)
    - North American Managers--CEO Review Group, 1998 (Box 26)
    - North American Managers--Photographs, 1999 (Box 26)
    - Office of the Chief Executive (OCE), 1996, 2001; 6 folders (Box 26)
    - Office of the Chief Executive (OCE), 2002 (Box 27)
    - Operations, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Patroon Group/CEO meeting, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Regional Directors, 1997 (Box 27)
    - Schedule for 1998 meetings (Box 27)
    - Senior Partners, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 27)
    - World Partners Council, 1995 (Box 27)
    - World Partners Council, 1995-1997; 6 folders (Box 28)
    - Worldwide Executive Group (WWEG), 1994-1997; 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Worldwide Executive Group (WWEG), 1997; 5 folders (Box 29)
    - Worldwide Executive Group (WWEG)/Board of Directors (BOD), 1997; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Worldwide Executive Group (WWEG)/Global Business, 1997 (Box 29)
    - Worldwide Executive Group (WWEG)/Global Business, 1997 (Box 30)
    - Worldwide Executive Group (WWEG)/Global Business--Key Issues, 1997 (Box 30)
    - Worldwide Operating Group (WWOG), 1994 (Box 30)
    - WPP Board, 1995 (Box 30)
  - Worldwide Executive Group (WWEG)/Global Business Group (GBG)/Board of Directors (BOD) Combined Files, 1996; 2
    - 1996 Feb.--Agendas, logistics, etc. (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Biltmore Hotel (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Correspondence (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Discussion on JWT minority partners and non-equity affiliates (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Emerging Multinational Review (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Forms (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Grid for Assessing Client Importance (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Management titles discussion (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Management vision statement (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Meetings schedules (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Multinational Accounts (Box 30)
    - 1996 Feb.--Multinational Accounts, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - 1996 Feb.--Multinational Client Status Report (Box 31)
    - 1996 Feb.--Strategic development (Box 31)
    - 1996 Feb.--WWEG action summary (Box 31)
    - 1996 May--Agendas, logistics, etc., 3 folders (Box 31)
    - 1996 May--Chris Jones dinner (Box 31)
    - 1996 May--JWT Asia Pacific Review (Box 31)
    - 1996 May--JWT credentials presentation (Box 31)
    - 1996 May--Kimberly Clark/Scott Brand (Box 31)
    - 1996 May--Media State of the Union (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--Meeting notes (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--Multinational Account Meeting (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--Print examples/slides (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--Strategic Plan summary (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--Summary of Feb. meeting (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--Thompson Total Branding: Converting the Creatives (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--Warner-Lambert dinner (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--Warner-Lambert global brand overview (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--Weighing Opportunities for Operational Improvement at a Local Office Level (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--Worldwide Partners list (Box 32)
    - 1996 May--WWEG summary of actions (Box 32)
    - 1996 July--Action plan, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - 1996 July--Agendas, logistics, etc., 2 folders (Box 32)
    - 1996 July--Financial Report (Box 32)
    - 1996 July--Ford Global Business Plan (Box 32)
    - 1996 July--Global Business Partnerships (Box 32)
    - 1996 July--JWT Asia Pacific Review (Box 32)
    - 1996 July--JWT Europe (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--JWT North America Office highlights (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--Media presentation (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--Nabisco (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--Nike Global Business Review (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--Non-Advertising Services Billing Practices for Top-10 Clients (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--Notes (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--Rolex 50th anniversary (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--Strategic Plan Summary (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--Summary of May meeting (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--Unilever (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--Website survey (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--WWEG action plan summary (Box 33)
    - 1996 July--WWEG meeting notes (Box 33)
    - 1996 Sept.--Agendas, logistics, etc., 2 folders (Box 33)
    - 1996 Sept.--Agendas, logistics, etc. (Box 65)
    - 1996 Sept.--Cross-reference of Directors of major JWT clients (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--Global Business Group--Financial reports (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--Global Business Group--Key issues by client (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--JWT Asia Pacific (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--JWT Europe (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--Logistics, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--Major issues for Global Business Group (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--Media procurement (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--Multinational Client Status Report (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--Notes (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--Photographs (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--Strategic Action Plan (Box 34)
    - 1996 Sept.--Topping Center for Total Branding (Box 34)
    - 1996 Nov.--Action points (Box 35)
    - 1996 Nov.--Agenda, schedules, etc., 3 folders (Box 35)
    - 1996 Nov.--Audiovisual support (Box 35)
    - 1996 Nov.--Board of Directors Meeting (Box 35)
    - 1996 Nov.--Board of Directors presentations (Box 35)
    - 1996 Nov.--Digital Decisions, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - 1996 Nov.--Direct Relationship Marketing (Box 35)
    - 1996 Nov.--Global Business Group (Box 35)
    - 1996 Nov.--Logo designs, etc. for meeting (Box 35)
    - 1996 Nov.--Meeting logistics, 5 folders (Box 36)
    - 1996 Nov.--Meeting schedules, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - 1996 Nov.--Meeting schedules, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - 1996 Nov.--Presentation materials (Box 37)
    - 1996 Nov.--Strategic Development Investment Plan (Box 37)
    - 1996 Nov.--Thompson Total Branding status (Box 37)
    - 1996 Nov.--Thompson Total Manning video project (Tribute to Burt Manning) (Box 37)
    - 1996 Nov.--Turnberry Isle (Box 37)
    - 1996 Nov.--Unilever Global Account Management (Box 37)
    - 1996 Nov.--Worldwide I.T. Status Report (Box 37)
- Memoranda, 1974-2003; 3
  - General, 1974-1998; 3
    - Burt Manning memo to all staff (not sent), 1992-1993 (Box 37)
    - Burt Manning to staff, 1994-1995 (Box 37)
    - Burt Manning Monthly Communications Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 37)
    - Cannes, 1997 (Box 37)
    - Cannes, 1997 (Box 38)
    - Changes I (binder), 1974-1988; 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Changes II (binder), 1988-1995 (Box 38)
    - Changes III (binder), 1996-1997 (Box 38)
    - Compilation list of staff memos, 1994-1997 (Box 38)
    - Good news/New business, 1986-1995 (Box 38)
    - JWT North America, 1998 (Box 38)
    - McCann-Erickson piracy of JWT intellectual property, 1995 (Box 38)
    - Senior management, 1991-1993; 3 folders (Box 38)
    - Senior management, 1994-1996; 4 folders (Box 39)
    - Total Solutions for Total Branding, 1998 (Box 39)
    - WPP share offer, 1987 (Box 39)
  - Obituaries for JWT staff, 1993-2003; 4
    - Bill Ross, 2003 (Box 39)
    - Clemens Hathaway, 1997 (Box 39)
    - Connie Ivey, 1996 (Box 39)
    - Edward G. Wilson, 1993 (Box 39)
    - Glen Fortinberry, 1993 (Box 39)
    - Howard Brundage, 1997 (Box 39)
    - Howard Kohl, 1993 (Box 39)
    - Ramon Masip, 1996 (Box 39)
    - Priscilla Meek, 1999 (Box 39)
    - Jack Peters, 1993 (Box 39)
    - John Monsarrat, 1995 (Box 39)
    - John Sharman, 1994 (Box 39)
    - Loy Baxter, 2003 (Box 39)
    - Manu Elexpuru, 1993 (Box 39)
    - Nancy Stephenson, 1998 (Box 39)
    - Norman Strouse, 1993 (Box 39)
    - Tom Sutton, 1994 (Box 39)
    - Shirley Woodell, 1996 (Box 39)
- Print Material, 1947-2000 and undated; 4
  - Account Management Career Path Program, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Ad Spending: Growing Market Share (James Schroer), 1990 (Box 40)
  - Advertising Age: 50 Years of TV Advertising, 1995 (Box 65)
  - Advertising Age: The Advertising Century, 1999 (Box 65)
  - Advertising Age: JWT 100th Anniversary, 1964 (Box 65)
  - Advertising Age: JWT 125th Anniversary, 1989 (Box 65)
  - Advertising Age: Latin American Marketing, 1998 (Box 40)
  - Adweek Global Quarterly: Asia, 1994 (Box 40)
  - Ascent of Woman, circa 1996 (Box 40)